literally tripling because they've
literalmente triplicando porque me han
done all the [ __ ] work for me
hecho todo el [__] trabajo
military worker from the dance class
trabajador militar de la clase de baile
something came up that was not at all
salió algo en lo que no estaba nada
clear at all to be direct very bored
claro nada a estar directo muy aburrido
nothing
nada
nothing relevant and taro like calm and
nada relevante y taro como tranquilito y
all you know I was here looking for things to
tal sabe estaba aquí buscando cosas que
comment on you know commenting above
comentar sabes comentando por encima
because he doesn't even know what's worth
porque es que no sabe ni que vale
this is already passed to another level this has already
esto ya pasa a otro nivel esto ya ha
passed to another level okay
pasado a otro nivel
we're not talking about he sent you
vale ya no estamos hablando de te mandó
an email and warned you about the sanse and everything no no no no I mean
un email y te avisó del sanse y todo no
this man literally did
no no no o sea es que literalmente este
a word okay
un word vale
my word
my word
literally I don't deserve the money I'm going to
literalmente no me merezco el dinero que
earn today he did
voy a ganar hoy
n't tell me anything I'm not going to charge for this video I'm
no me dijo nada este vídeo no me lo voy
going to charge for not working
a cobrar voy a cobrar por no trabajar
as if I were a mattress tester
como si fuera un probador de colchones
Javier the best video I've ever seen
javier el mejor vídeo que yo haya visto
was that one and the thing is that in life it's
fue ese y es que en la vida es
the internet it's life gentlemen karma apparently because
internet es la vida señores karma la
of what I've done
por lo visto por lo he hecho ha pasado
something happened in kárbala okay there was salsa in
algo en kárbala vale ha habido salsa en
carbones I have no [ __ ] idea what
carbones no tengo ni [__] idea de lo que
happened the only thing I've received are
ha pasado lo único que me ha llegado son
a lot of emails telling me that before the
mucho email diciéndome que antes a la
series that has ended because  someone did
serie que se ha terminado porque alguien
n't want to pay for the server I don't know what's
no quería pagar el servidor no sé qué
up so we're going to find out
movida así que nos vamos a enterar
because this kid here but from here
porque este chaval aquí pero de aquí
all the fun buddy
todo de la gracia colega
plus this has this happen or rather
además que esto tiene esto ocurra o sea
colors purple vegetable green willis
de colores morado vegetal verde willis
blue to the fbi
de azul al fbi
has taken out his tail guy takes out his tail
se ha sacado el rabo tío se saca el rabo
kárbala what is it is a minecraft series
kárbala que es es una serie de minecraft
created by the great vegetable where several
creada por el gran vegetal donde varios
youtubers play on an online server I
youtuber juegan en un servidor online me
love it because he made me like an
encanta porque me ha hecho como una
intro done this I think he
intro hecho esto yo creo que él me ha
wanted to make me a script for a video
querido hacer un guión para un vídeo
for the main channel and I study here
para el canal principal y estudio aquí
super lazy that I'm here super value
súper vago que estoy aquí súper valor
reading he told me my egg in the
leyendo me lo contó mi huevo en el
live guy good to move it to see if it's
directo tío bueno a moverlo a ver si
good
está bueno
carvalho what is intro ok to put it in
carvalho que es intro ok para poner en
context so that he doesn't know what they are
contexto para que no sepa lo que
digging like the example well I do know
escarban como el ejemplo bueno yo sí sé
what a camera is but come on
lo que es cámara pero vamos
until recently I didn't know
hasta hace poco no sabía
the series has a general story
la serie cuenta con una historia general
that advances through each episode they are the
que avanza por cada episodio son los
so-called gods in parentheses the
llamados dioses entre paréntesis los
server administrators who are in
administradores del servidor quienes se
charge of advancing the story of the
encargan de avanzar la historia del
game through events we have seen
juego por medio de eventos hemos visto
halloween christmas valentine's day
halloween navidad san valentín
etcetera the first season of  karma
etcétera la primera temporada de karma
started in 2017 I understand I make them a thousand
se inició en 2017 entiendo los hago mil
0 from July to no no no no there is a number left
0 de julio a no no no no sobra un número
okay it is July 21 2014 and it featured
vale es el 21 de julio de 2014 y contaba
the youtubers vegeta willy alex and
con los youtubers vegeta willy alex y
stack okay the second season
stack vale la segunda temporada se
opened on August 8 where I
inauguró el 8 de agosto en donde yo
study this is this is history
estudio esto es esto es historia
this that has prepared for me this is
esto que me ha preparado esto es
history I have you explode you know
historia os tengo explota sabes
okay here the fbi was missing okay 2015 in the
vale aquí faltaba al fbi vale 2015 en la
third season the
tercera temporada volvían a estar los
four vouchers were back in 2017 this season was
cuatro vales en 2017 esta temporada se
filled with controversy this is where
llenó de polémica aquí es donde empezó
the conflict between stack and willy began it is
el conflicto entre stack y willy se
discussed what caused
comenta qué es lo que hizo que se
the series to close the fourth season the
cerrase la serie la cuarta temporada la
last one we saw started on October 7
última que vimos se inició el 7 octubre
2019 which was the one that hit very hard
de 2019 que fue la que pegó muy fuerte
that was already euros in play okay here it says
que ya estaba euro en play vale aquí
euros play luso for ruby ​​an
pone euros play luso para el rubí un
angel and lolito also okay link
ángel y lolito también vale link
want to open this link of course
desea abrir este vínculo claro
life
la vida
or rather this is so that people don't come
o sea esto es para que no venga la peña
tell me let's see what you are basing your
decirme a ver en qué te basas
source on
fuente
go and confirm it to me
vayan y me lo confirmó
incredible incredible I'm going to hire this
increíble increíble voy a contratar este
guy to write the scripts for the
tipo para que me haga los guiones de los
videos to take by ass and so I'm not
vídeos a tomar por culo y así que no
making a truth
hago una verdad
this season was special because he
esta temporada fue especial porque
managed to bring together a lot of youtubers
consiguió reunir a muchísimos youtubers
and it was also the first to have
y además fue la primera en contar con
the aforementioned gods,
los dioses antes mencionados
that is, in the other season they handled
o sea en la otra temporada se manejaba
half 4 and they put together their story okay
medio 4 y se montaban su historia vale
but in this last one where the
pero ya en esta última que estaban los
eight youtubers were also well they are all
youtubers ochos también bueno son todos
names well
nombres bueno
the blond euro was added well it seems that he
se añadió el rubio euros pues se ve que
had people on the server hired
tenía gente en el servidor contratada
to put together the events and
para que ese montarse en los eventos y
the stories okay
las historias vale esto también lo
we also have this on the front
tenemos nosotros en fachada
well it lasted two days but there were
bueno que duró dos días pero había
kids no we do
chavales no
n't know their identities or how many there
no conocemos sus identidades ni cuántos
are but I suppose they are a
son pero supongo que son un equipo
pretty big team
bastante grande
the events were huge and everything was
los eventos eran gigantes y todo estaba
created by the gods also with
creado por los dioses además siempre con
youtube it was always direct there was one or two
youtube era sea directo había uno o dos
gods in the game checking that the
dioses en la partida revisando que el
game worked well
juego funcione bien
the youtubers paid a salary to the
los youtubers pagaban un sueldo a los
gods obviously and to the
dioses obvios y a los moderadores de
kárbala moderators as the story progressed they
kárbala conforme avanzaba en la historia
needed to hire more people more
necesitaron contratar a más gente más
as they progressed in the story
conforme avanzan en la historia
they needed to hire more people in
necesitaron contratar a más gente en
this video that I pass you vegeta  account that they
este vídeo que te paso vegeta cuenta que
had to hire a person
tuvieron que contratar a una persona
to pull the videos that people
para que tire los vídeos que la gente
received to youtube minutes 045 this this
recibía a youtube minutos 045 este este
this I think is right we reacted
esto creo que derecho lo reaccionamos
here but where I do is that I don't know
aquí pero donde yo hago es eso no sé
how to report it to truth
cómo reportarlo a verdad
by the way we saw this here
por cierto esto lo vimos aquí
let's see it again you put it it's not
vamos a volverlo a ver os lo pones no
worth it message to live be clear
vale mensaje para vivir ser claro
subnormal subnormal you know that then they
subnormales subnormales sabes que luego
go through life as poor things you touch my
van de pobrecitos por la vida me toquéis
balls with both hands to start with
los huevos a dos manos para empezar a
that one who uploads any video
aquel aquel que suba a cualquier vídeo
of our colleagues that we have had to
de nuestros compañeros que hemos tenido
take a person simply for that is
[__] una persona simplemente para eso
worth it the one who uploads the videos strike
vale aquel que suba los vídeos strike
vegetable or I do not want private absurd
vegetal o no quiero privado absurdo
saying vegetable I do it because I am
diciendo vegetal yo lo hago porque soy
a fan and my balls my balls well that you
un fan y mis huevos mis huevos bien que
monetize it and well that you take the
lo monetizar y bien que te llevas el
money silly I have been
dinero tontito
here enough years to know
llevo suficientes años aquí para saber
what it does it is the same if you do not choose the
lo que hace es igual si no eliges el
video and you do it what it does is upload
vídeo y lo haces lo que hace es subir
200 videos gain subscribers you change the
200 vídeos ganar suscriptores cambias el
format of the channel you have kept the
formato del canal te has quedado con los
subscribers delete the videos and make
suscriptores elimina los vídeos y haces
your channel with the best 300,000
tu canal con la mejor 300.000
subscribers you
suscriptores
must be subnormal [ __ ] and for
hay que ser subnormal [__] y por
that reason and  that's why we who are
ello y por ello nosotros que estamos
here day after day doing hours and hours of
aquí día a día haciendo horas y horas de
live are
directo
telling you directly to
te decimos directamente que lo quites
please and kindly remove it and this is the
por favor y amablemente y es el aviso
official notice that we give the next one is the
que damos oficial el siguiente es el
strike that will fall on you tomorrow in fact
strike que te va a caer mañana de hecho
what I'm doing and the person who is in
lo que estoy haciendo y la persona que
charge of doing that we are
está encargada de hacer eso estamos
waiting for those two videos or three
esperando aquellas dos vídeos o tres
videos and we directly close the channel and
vídeos y directamente cerramos canal y
automatically the income that you have
automáticamente los ingresos que hayas
generated with that video goes to
generado con ese vídeo pasando a
us and we will look for a service well
nosotros y buscaremos un servicio bueno
this is what vegeta said not like that if
esto es lo que ha dicho vegeta no así si
you have three videos at once in the
tú tienes tres vídeos de golpe en el
same day, three don't get three trails,
mismo día no le caen tres trail le cae
one gets it okay it counts as one and you can
uno vale cuenta como uno y la
no longer
monetización ya no la puedes no la
claim the monetization after what had
puedes reclamar después lo que había
generated being yours a legal one which is
generado siendo suyos uno legal que es
where we can sue and request the
donde podamos demandar y solicitar el
income that has been made to you for the
ingreso que se te haya hecho por los
videos that you have not that yes that yes it can be
vídeos que nos has eso sí eso sí se
done that yes
puede hacer eso sí
by the way it seems relevant to me to comment
por cierto me parece relevante comentar
then if I'm going to find it on the go take
entonces si lo voy a encontrar a marcha
a look if we find it [ __ ] I'm
un vistazo si lo encontramos fuck voy
welcome thank you very much I
bienvenido muchas gracias
find it okay it's not going to
yo encuentro vale tampoco me va a
complicate me much either I'll find it quickly
complicar mucho se lo encuentro rápido
yes and if not no
sí y si no no
and apparently vegeta was
y es que por lo visto vegeta me estuvo
mentioning me in another live that we didn't
mencionando en otro directo que no lo
see  they
vimos
proposed recently it has to be
propusieron hace poco sea tiene que
you and over here
estar tú y por aquí
see this I know you and it seems that this one who
ven esta te conozco y parece que este
sees you I don't know why he follows me on
que te ve yo no sé por qué me sigue en
the networks on this twitter I don't know if he
las redes en este twitter no sé si me
follows me on the other cms guide but install
sigue en el otro cms guía pero instalar
so he follows me and we'll talk a few
así que me sigue y vamos a hablar unas
times there's a really good guy really
veces no hay un chaval buenísimo
good a lot of people also I think he
buenísimo muchísima gente además creo
's my age don't see being my
que es de mi quinta no ve estando de mi
age super super nice guy super
quinta chaval súper súper majo supermajo
nice guy really nice guy I can't say anything bad about
tío majísimo no puedo decir nada malo de
Vegeta come on super good
vegeta vengáis súper bien
[Applause] I do
[Aplausos]
n't know to what extent watch my videos and
no sé hasta qué punto ver a mis vídeos y
stuff but here and on Friday
esas cosas pero acá y el viernes por la
morning
mañana
who says Tibet shot that was
quien dice tíbet shot que se entendió
perfectly understood spoken I tried the one in
perfectamente hablado probé el que
minutes at 18 to see if it
minutos en el 18 a ver
left you
te dejaba
vegetal know
vegetal saber
a channel by
un canal de
Javier Canijo
javier canijo
and this seems to me one of the most
y esto me parece uno de los cambios más
important changes in our history it
importantes de nuestra historia
seems to me one of the strongest changes
me parece uno de los cambios más fuertes
in life it
de la vida es
seems to me a change PSOE it seems to me a
me parece un cambio psoe me parece un
change
cambio
now I'm going to give it back to you vegetables from
ahora te la voy a devolver vegetales de
here thank you very much for recommending me
aquí muchas gracias por recomendarme
okay and from here tell all my
vale y desde aquí decirle a toda mi
people to subscribe to vegetar
gente que se suscriban a vegetar
knew  that I pay my debts it has
sabía que yo pago mis deudas
always been said that entering
siempre se ha dicho que entran en
Karbala is very difficult since as is
kárbala es muy difícil ya que como es
normal you have to be friends with everyone to
normal hay que ser amigo de todos para
enter obviously
entrar obvio
obviously
obvio
Dallas would enter no because in this case he has
dallas entraría no porque en este caso
had conflicts with the FBI and Rubio
ha tenido conflictos con el fbi y rubio
for example not to always mention
por ejemplo para no mencionar siempre a
Dallas another example we saw it on the internet
dallas otro ejemplo lo vimos en internet
or in an episode they talked about Karma la
o en un capítulo hablaron sobre karma la
so he was looking forward to entering and he
por lo que estaba deseando entrar e
even made a song for
incluso hizo una canción para que
Vegetables to point out Dario commented that it is
vegetales apunte darío comentó que es
very difficult to enter that since the humor has
muy difícil entrar que como el humor tan
been so Orlov's it would not be possible he said
ha sido de orlov no se podría dijo
also why do you think Percy has
además porque te crees que percy estás
not entered because he is the friend of
no ha entrado porque que es el amigo de
these people to enter implying
esta gente para entrar dando a entender
that there was a conflict between hangers and let's
que existía un conflicto entre perchas y
see
es que a ver
that they would not make sense if not I mean
que no tendrían sentido si no ósea
yes yes I have a series with four
sí sí yo tengo una serie con cuatro
colleagues the most logical thing is that I only
colegas lo más lógico es que solamente
recorded with us in the series of
grabé con nosotros en la serie de
our colleagues if you want to play
nuestros colegas si tú quieres jugar
creature series with yours what is the point of us
creatura serie con lo tuyo qué sentido
putting water in the series with
tiene que metamos en la serie agua con
us area and that we know each other
nosotros área y que nos conocemos
we are recording our moves not
estamos grabando nuestras movidas no
a change in Karma la of it seems to me a
un cambio en karma la de me parece una
very important thing to put in my
cosa muy importante que poner en mi
resume
currículum
imply that there is a conflict
dan a entender que existe un conflicto
between present vegetable I have not been able to
entre presente vegetal no he podido
find click I'm very sorry because I
encontrar clic lo siento mucho porque
would have been
habría estado
[ __ ] he is apologizing he is
[__] está disculpando se está
apologizing because he has not been able to
disculpando porque no me ha podido
find me a clip of why persita is
encontrar un clip de porque persita está
fighting with vegetable
peleado con vegetal
hey well look if someone wants to finish it is
oye pues mira si alguien quiere terminar
going to be work for me because that kid
me va a ser trabajo porque ese chaval
who had fired him for the genome click
que lo había despedido por el genoma
positions okay
puestos de clic vale
and so you look for all this click we
y así me buscáis todo esto clic
achieved this video for each
lo logramos este vídeo para cada
main I had little shame
principal tuve poca vergüenza
well I don't know we did
bueno no sé
n't think about it I have swallowed all the
no lo pensamos me he tragado todos los
episodes of I internet or I love it
episodios de yo internet o me encanta
but I can't remember where it says
pero no consigo recordar dónde lo dice
click where the fate of the
el click donde que se pele el sino del
internet is fought or look for you there with the number of hours
internet o busca tu ahí con la de horas
that are that no now we go to the salsero to
que son eso no ahora vamos al salsero a
the insult what we care about he hires him again
la injuria lo que a nosotros nos bola lo
look at you the kid doing goes here the
fíjate tú el chaval haciendo va aquí el
[ __ ] god and adam puts there his his
[__] dios y adam le mete ahí su su
comment of the director his comments
comentario del director sus comentarios
but here nothing about my cousin's panties
pero aquí nada de las bragas de mi prima
or anything like that don't be something private he doesn't
ni na de eso no sea algo privado no le
put emphasis there what we
pone énfasis ahí lo que a nosotros nos
like insult as if we liked to
gusta la injuria como si nos gustara
insult people what we like  is
injuriar a la gente lo que nos gusta es
when one fights over another and they
cuando uno se pelea por otro y se
report each other and so on no
denuncian y demás no
angel was the first to leave
ángel fue el primero en abandonar
kárbala because we have already screwed up why
kárbala pues ya la hemos cagado por qué
angel angel is that I did not realize
ángel ángel es que no me di cuenta de
when he is not even if they put your
cuándo está ni aunque te pongan tu
name son
nombre hijo
after a few weeks he left after a few
a las pocas semanas se fue al cabo de
months he would come back but it lasted for a few
los meses volvía a entrar pero duraba
days because because man is
días contados porque porque el hombre es
a striped of life lolito lasted longer
un rayado de la vida lolito duró más
he was very addicted at the beginning he
tiempo estuvo muy viciado al principio
dedicated many hours he talked about live shows
le dedicó muchas horas habló de directos
of 8 hours playing minecraft look and he
de 8 horas jugando a minecraft miras y
put it now that the gods had to
le puso ahora que los dioses tuvieron
put a time restriction so
que poner una restricción de tiempo para
that no one was above the
que nadie estuviera por encima los
kids screaming explode not when
chavales a gritos explotar no cuando
the virality of gta role play began he
empezó la viralidad de gta role play se
left karma land and left there very
marchó de karma land y se fue de ahí muy
well lolito pointing tar carrey for the
bien lolito apuntando tar carrey por las
visits and then another fashion comes out and of
visitas y luego sale otra moda y de
activity to the colleagues of [ __ ] great I
actividad a los colegas de [__] madre me
imagine it would be like that having been the
imagino que sería así habernos sido el
content of invented the comments
contenido de inventó los comentarios
I am making it is with sarcasm valeri
estoy haciendo es con sarcasmo valeri
with a joke
con broma
because I do not know the context maybe I
porque no sé el contexto a lo mejor
am right but I do not know
estoy acertando pero no lo sé
toño of lost
toño de perdido
the case was to the sun where  more heats
el caso fue al sol donde más calienta
valera it's a fact aurum term in
valera es un hecho aurum término entre
quotes calmly land when the
comillas con calma land cuando empezó el
vision gta started well in fact I don't think
vision gta bueno de hecho creo que no
so even doing gta when he could
que incluso haciendo a gta cuando podía
dedicate some time to micro he also
dedicarle un rato a micro también lo
did it from then on he entered
hacía es a partir de ahí entró mucho
minecraft much less he didn't abandon it completely it
menos a minecraft no lo abandonó todo
must be said but he did enter once
hay que decirlo pero sí que entraba una
or twice a week instead of
o dos veces a la semana en lugar de
every day like before you know it's
todos los días como antes sabes que es
normal that now they have abandoned the
normal que ahora tengan abandonado el
main channel because he's dedicating
canal principal porque le está dedicando
a lot to this
mucho a esto
the blond more of the same he was entering less and
el rubio más de lo mismo fue entrando
less to carvalho by the
cada vez menos a carvalho ya para el
end he had completed all the
final había completado todos los
challenges and explored the entire area so he did
desafíos y explorado toda la zona por lo
n't have much else to do he got
que no tenía mucho más que hacer se
bored and ended up entering about
aburrió y terminó entrando unas dos
twice a week
veces a la semana
click of the blond talking about the people who
clic del rubio hablando de la gente que
left
lo dejó
many of us have stopped doing
muchos de nosotros hemos dejado de hacer
so much live camera not even that
tanto directo de cámara ni eso
sofovich dude put the [ __ ] clip on me he
sofovich tío me ha puesto el [__] clip
put the [ __ ] clip on me
me ha puesto el [__] clip
at the minute that is the literal I'm
en el minuto que es el literal me estoy
[ __ ] my balls
tocando los huevos
with so much constancy he means or rather
con tanta constancia quiere decir o sea
we haven't left with some and like
no lo hemos dejado con algunos y en plan
angel left calm down for that ray and such
ángel dejó calma por ese rayo y tal
now he does less and less but that's not  It
ahora un cada vez hace menos pero eso no
means like it
significa en plan
means that they also ended due to
significa que también acabaron por
loss of hype or they were given a final episode.
pérdida de hype o les dieron episodio
We are clear that yes, we do not
nosotros tenemos claro que sí que no
want to let it die on the air without
queremos dejar que muera en plana sin
more, that little by little people leave and that it
más que poco a poco la gente se vaya y
ends like other karmans in
que acabe en plan como otros karman en
which is what I understand that ending
que es lo que tengo entendido que acabar
in a somewhat bland way, not in a
en plan de manera un poco sosa no en
plan what we want to do is if we make
plan lo que queremos hacer es si hacer
an ending, obviously that we are
un final pues obviamente que estemos
all going to do it, in fact in the end the
todos lo hicieran de hecho al final la
majority or so end up burning out and if we
mayoría o así acaban quemamos y si
get to the end
llegamos al final
after this June is done, if I want it to be, well, I
después de hecho esto junio si quiero
say look, this is the
que sea pues ya decir mira esto ya es el
end, we are going to make a cool payment, you know, it doesn't
final vamos a hacer un pago guay sabéis
have to be the right moment but we are
no tiene por qué ser momento pero vamos
all going to get together
a juntarnos todos y
and we are going to say goodbye
y vamos a despedirla por lo menos sabes
at least you know, but if there is now we will see the video if you want, Aura Lolito and the Blonde were the ones who gave the most substance to the story, the Portuguese FBI and Fargas are not funny, they do not have that roguishness of the others, they have horchata in Lasarte Oria these phrases of mine,
en lasarte oria estas frases mías
this phrase this follower is a big follower of
esta frase este seguidor es muy seguidor
mine without the key pieces of the game, they will
mía sin las piezas claves del juego
calm down, they felt a very big delay
calmaran sintió un retraso muy grande
man rubin didn't have the blonde the
hombre el rubin no tenía al rubio el
blonde was smart and they were still the ones with the most
rubio lo listo y aún eran los que más
hunger
chicha de hambre
[ __ ] vegetable is dedicated to that it doesn't have
[__] vegetal se dedica a eso no tiene
much success I imagine that something powerful
mucho éxito me imagino que algo potente
area not always that vegeta what happens
área no siempre que vegeta lo que pasa
is that mike goes up it was equally I don't know
es que sube mike era igualmente no sé
although it is not they calmed down there is no need to
aunque no sea se calmaran no hace falta
calm lamp such no the
calma lámpara tal no
end of the series there has been no end it
el final de la serie no ha habido final
is something that the youtubers stay a
es algo que los youtubers se quedan
lot there
mucho
was no end I thought I saw around there about
no hubo un final me pareció ver por ahí
a month or two months ago that
hace cosa de un mes o dos meses que
they did some kind of event something no no there were no
hicieron una especie de evento algo no
cars I wouldn't know how to put it
no hubo coches no sabría ponernos ahora
in context now what I saw then
en contexto qué fue lo que vi entonces
but I thought I saw
pero me pareció ver
something together they did
algo juntos hicieron
now a matter two minus two months in
ahora cuestión dos menos dos meses en
it after those of gta this the roll there
ella después de los de gta esto el rollo
was something one day that they all did and I
hubo algo un día que hicieron todos y
think almost all of them were there it
creo que estaban casi todos
was to sell the play 5 to the one that
era para vender la play 5 a la de me
fell on me the biggest problem is that the
cayó el problema más grande es que los
youtubers in which they left it there are
youtubers en los que se lo dejaron
those who say that it is because gta
hay quien dice que es porque empezó gta
roll plate started that there were other fashionable games
roll plate que hubo otros juegos de moda
but the truth is that there are many who
pero la verdad es que hay muchos que
accuse the youtubers who left the
acusan a los youtubers que dejaron el
game all without saying names as you would
juego todo sin decir nombres como se
expect from these people yes  because they don't
cabe esperar de esta gente sí porque no
like the salsa and the gossip of
les gusta el salsero y el cuchichear de
one from the other time say things
uno del otro tiempo decir las cosas
clearly you
claras
can stay no matter how much it is
se puede quedar por mucho que esté de
fashionable people have and no matter how much then
moda la gente ha y por mucho que luego
the fall guy and no matter how much then my
el fall guy y por mucho que luego mi
dick in vinegar you stay one day hey
[__] en vinagre quedáis un día oye
let's close this see what we do little
vamos a cerrar esto vea qué hacemos poco
more as a final chapter what do we do
más como capítulo final que hacemos
come for a party we all
venga por una fiesta todo
throw rockets and see you later if you don't
tiramos cohetes y hasta luego si no lo
do it it's because there is a bad vibe if you don't do it it
hace es porque hay es un mal rollo si no
's because there is some problem
lo hace es porque hay algún problemilla
okay we do
vale
n't know what but there is one it
no sabemos cuál pero lo hay
is true that there is a certain
sí que es verdad que hay una cierta
apathy between the people of kárbala and the
apatía entre la gente de kárbala y la
people of the role play of aurum we see it in
gente del role play de aurum lo vemos en
love for example there are two groups of
amor por ejemplo hay dos grupos de
Spanish youtubers very different
youtuber españoles bien diferenciados
that do not usually mix the group d auro
que no se suelen mezclar el grupo d auro
and the group of vegeta willy and company that is to
y el grupo de vegeta willy y compañía es
say carmarán against gta role play
decir carmarán contra gta role play ahí
something big happened there that we cannot know the
pasó algo gordo que no podemos saber el
click that passed you by instagram of willy
click que te pase por instagram de willy
red
red
covering a special event if the
abarcando un evento especial si el
problem with karma land is that in the end
problema de karma land es que al final
many people left it aside of those of us who
mucha gente lo dejo de lado de los que
are on the server they left said there are
estamos en el servidor se fueron dicho
people  who owes money to the
hay gente que debe hasta dinero a la
people on the server who actually had to put up
gente del servidor que tuvo que poner de
the money vegetal
hecho el dinero vegetal
who is going to who is going to owe money who is
quién va a quién va a deber dinero quién
going to leave money to owe there
va a dejar dinero a deber
are people who left money without paying to
hay gente que dejo dinero sin pagar a
the gods I mean it
los dioses
seems strange to me the money
o sea me parece raro las pastas que
these people earn for breakfast ronchi
ganan esta gente para desayuna ronchi
there
allá
better
mejor
as very ugly you know nothing they entered
como muy feo sabes nada entraron a
carmela they did well they
carmela les fue bien
got visits subscribers I don't know what
cogieron visitas suscriptores no sé qué
and when it was no longer useful to them well they
y cuando ya no les sirvió pues le dio
kicked him they kicked him well
una patada le dieron una patada pues
this smells like see we can't confirm
esto huele a ver no podemos afirmar
because they are giving very little and without name
porque están dando poquita y sin nombre
but it smells like what is legal it smells like
pero huele a lo lícito
lolita they
huele a lolita
came they got it for fashion visit of
vinieron lo cogieron por moda visita de
pim pam pam and then they slept with one I
pim pam pam y después se tiraron a uno
tell you that he has not left one
ya te digo yo que a uno no ha dejado
money and I trust dv I
pasta y a dv confío en él
trust him completely
confío plenamente en él
the blond not a chance neither does ruben navas that's what he
el rubio ni de coña tampoco rubén navas
calls ruby ​​gets along super well
eso llama el rubí se lleva súper bien
with vegeta and willy I
con vegeta y willy
mean
o sea
the suspicions would be between mangel
las sospechas estarían entre mangel
lolito
lolito
between more general and tone
entre más general y tono
with light or he could also charge they
con luz o también podría cargar
could or it could be the four and so
podrían o podrían ser los cuatro y así
basically it's a bit like  that made me
básicamente es un poco como que me dio
angry about Carmona next time
rabia por la próxima vez de carmona
we'll talk differently and whoever doesn't meet
hablaremos distinto y quien no cumple
the requirements to do it, well I know
los requisitos de hacer pues yo que sé
about getting into the flesh at least once a
de entrar la carne al menos una vez a la
week, well out of here and that's it, we don't
semana pues fuera de aquí y ya está no
only
solamente queremos gente activa solos
want active people alone, so if in the end you're in Carnal and there are the usual three or four of us, well, they take away your permanent contract to earn the truth and that's why we stopped going exclusivity we left the series too for a bit and nothing we had many more events in mind but
muchos más eventos en la cabeza pero
we said we'll do a next season and we'll be there
decimos haremos una próxima temporada y
for people who like it
estaremos ya pues por gente que le guste
more and take it more seriously and all
más y se lo tome más en serio y todo
this when someone leaves the series when I
esto cuando alguien se vaya de la serie
arrive I'm leaving the series to leave
llegado yo me voy de la serie dejar
room for someone else you know if we had
hueco a otra persona sabe si hubiésemos
warned, well I or anyone else a
avisado pues yo o sea a cualquier otro a
lot of people it's that they would only have been
mucha gente es que solamente hubiese
interested
interesado
look what appears here we told it
mirad lo que aparece aquí lo contábamos
with this Rubio reacts and gives his opinion to Willy they
con esto rubio reacciona y opina a willy
talk about why they left Karbala
se habla de por qué dejaron kárbala
always this guy plays music
siempre este cabrón pone música
but people left him about
pero la gente lo dejo de
Rubin I don't know let's not even [ __ ] with him
el rubin no sé vamos a ni de coña en de
if
si quiere
he wants to here I'm going to say that I  I owe money I
yo aquí voy a decir que yo debo dinero
paid I don't know if for a month or two but I
yo pagué no sé si un mes o dos pero yo
paid
pagué
and he's going to say that in ugly
y va a decir que en feo de siniestros
public claims that some of the others owe
públicos que algunos de los otros deben
money but of course the truth is that [ __ ]
dinero pero claro es que en verdad que
them you go to the strip of the
les den por culo sales a la tira de la
series and on top of that they had to put up
serie y encima han tenido que poner
the money themselves of course I
ellos el dinero por sí claro
left with my head held high
me fui con la cabeza bien alta
cruel and a little smile
cruel y sonrisita
because at first it was always like they
porque al principio siempre era como que
put restrictions on us entering
nos ponían restricciones para entrar a
coal sometimes because we entered
carbón a veces porque entrábamos
too much on the road for example what the
demasiado por la vía por ejemplo lo que
kid just told me
acaba de contarme el chaval
I liked it wasn't because of the visit and anything
me gustaba no era por la visita y nada
because I really liked it he's inside
porque me gustaba de verdad está dentro
kallman building doing [ __ ]
de kallman construyendo haciendo [__]
I'm I stopped getting involved in the end it
yo estoy deje de meterme al final
was basically because of that because I no longer
fue básicamente por eso porque ya no
had anything to do like I had no
tenía nada que hacer en plan no tenía
goals
objetivos
your truth or that I talk how is that
su verdad o que hable como es eso
also clouded I understand what he wanted to do
también empañó entiendo lo que quería
the voucher is what he wanted to do was
hacer el vale es lo que quería hacer era
that we didn't
que no
finish the series in a week
acabamos la serie en una semana
we were like nine months old and we still hadn't
llevábamos como nueve meses y todavía no
gone out to explore
habíamos salido a explorar en plan
freely
libremente
freely that maybe the motorcycle ones that there
libremente que quizás la de motos que
were still to do
había todavía por hacer
and it's something that I was always saying that it
y es algo que siempre estaba diciendo
is minecraft they are series that can
que es minecraft son series que pueden
be infinite  gods that are so many
ser infinitas dioses que son tantísimas
possibilities of things of the
la posibilidad de las cosas de las
moves that can be invented and such that
movidas que se pueden inventar y tal que
can be can last do whatever they want
puede ser puede durar hacerle lo que les
how many
cuantos
I with exploring would be happy in order to
yo con explorar sería feliz en para
make myself firm with my plane you know to
hacerme firme con mi avión sabéis a
live in a [ __ ] jungle that was
vivir en una [__] jungla que estuviera a
50 million kilometers from the
50 millones de kilómetros de pueblo
main town of calm you know
principal de calma sabéis
and there does my [ __ ] it is but I don't know I
y ahí hace mi [__] es pero no sé
said time I don't know
dije tiempo no sé
but well that I understand 21 also what I
pero bueno que entiendo 21 también lo
wanted there was
que quería
a bad vibe I don't know we're not going I don't
había un mal rollo no sé no vamos no
think we know which one
creo que sepamos cuál
[Music] I've
[Música]
been carrying those combos egg tables or
llevo 15 meses esos combos huevo mesas o
rather the firm one
sea el firme
hey the blond also has a
oye el rubio también tiene corazón
purple heart purple heart
morado corazón morado
[Music]
[Música]
eleonora many truths and things
eleonora muchas verdades y cosas
we're waiting for it to be we'll do it I've already
estamos esperando que esté hacemos ya lo
said it we're at least
he dicho estamos a menos
this waterproof wagon is worth
este vagón impermeable vale
where we're going he says that there are people who
por donde vamos dice que hay gente que
stopped paying the administrators
dejó de pagar a los administradores
suspicions point to mangel saur
las sospechas apuntan a mangel saur
alone now let's see I don't
solito ahora yo vamos a ver
know him that well either but I
tampoco lo conozco tanto pero yo
would bet that it's not
apostaría que no es
ah and that sounded like an angel or the smart one
ah y eso ha sonado a ángel oa lo listo
because he brought up the subject of the
porque ha metido el tema de lo de la
cargo no  It was fashionable then it is not
carga no estaba de moda luego no está de
fashionable know what I'm telling you and now he didn't
moda saber lo que te digo y ahora no lo
abandon it, eradicate it, he didn't leave them stranded, he
abandonó erradicar no los dejó tirados
kept getting in at least once or twice
se seguía metiendo al menos una o dos
a week, okay,
veces a la semana vale
Angel collaborates with Willy in the entire Gaming
ángel colabora con willy en todo gaming
Academy and now he's a saint, the truth is he was
academy y ahora es un santo la verdad
playing with Luz recently, I
estuvo jugando con luz hace poco yo
personally lean towards Lolita, she
personalmente me inclino hacia lolita
has all the appearance, being the appearance,
tiene toda la pinta siendo la pinta
you know if she supports me, I'd be pissed off to let whoever it is, whoever
sabes si apoya me jodería dejar pasar el
left me, stop
que sea el que sea que haya dejado deja
seeing money because most of these
de ver pasta que la mayoría de estos
people are also earning rap, whoever it is that did
encima están ganando rap el que sea que
stop me from drinking money is already
sí me haya dejado de beber pasta ya les
worth it to them, I mean, the sailor cloth that
vale o sea que la tela marinera que lo
does the best but he wants to take you down maybe
haga lo mejor pero te quiere bajar
then he'll come out and talk about
a lo mejor luego sale y hablar
why
por qué
this happened to me because he got me into
me pasó esto porque me ha metido en
dubbing, we don't know either, we're not
doblas no sabemos tampoco no estamos
in it but [ __ ] if not so much
dentro pero [__] si no tan solo tanto
in public because they're freaked out by whoever
en público porque están rayada por el
left me owing money, you know and
que haya dejado a deber a pasta sabes y
on top of that, he had [ __ ] as a jerk,
encima que él haya tenido por hebe jeta
we also have a click of the blond
tenemos también un clic del rubio
talking about the same subject, I imagine it
hablando del mismo tema me imagino que
will be the same click, we just saw it,
será el mismo clic acabamos de verlo
this kid hasn't left anything out, I
este chaval no se ha dejado nada me
had, I had put the clip here,
había me había puesto aquí el clip
click of Auro  We already know that one does not get
clic de auro ya sabemos que a uno no se
wet there will not be a waterproof wagon children
moja no habrá un vagón impermeable hijos
say the karma problem is due to
dicen el problema de karma la se debe a
the visits
las visitas
to the visit the problem will be due
a la visita se va a deber el problema
what do I know
qué sé yo
to the visit and biting to finish
a la visita y mordiendo para acabar ya
a little if I can't talk to you can you
un poco si no lo puedo hablarte puedes
send a blessing to Valentina with
enviarle una bendición a valentina con
the old super homeless man he was offended by
el viejo super indigente se ofendió por
Bastía how disgusting how disgusting this channel is not
bastía qué asco qué asco este canal no
summarizes the other so
sea resume lo otro so
and puts this
y le pone esto
of a piece of ground and puts this
de suelo trozo y le pone esto
and here is the image and puts these
y aquí está la imagen y le pone estos
teeth
dientes
bald pad ww are you a good man
calvo almohadilla ww eres hombre bueno
then well
entonces pues bueno
without any other option I will have to talk about
sin más remedio tendré que hablar de que
the program friends I
el programa amigos
love you let's
te quiero
see if one day I do something with light or
a ver si algún día hago algo con luz o
I would like it happens that the truth is that I don't know
me gustaría pasa que la verdad que no sé
much about it
mucho de él
we have spoken on twitter sometimes
hemos hablado por twitter alguna vez
but no I don't know much about it let's see if we
pero no no sé mucho de él a ver si
coincide one day in another game something that
coincidimos algún día en otro juego algo
I with lights with those with whom I get along
que yo con luces con los que me llevo
well with everyone the truth happens
bien con todo el mundo la verdad pasa
that they calm down because it ended and it ended that's it
que calmaran pues terminó y terminó ya
people stopped coming in and there
está la gente dejó de entrar y ahí se
the series stayed it is that there is not there is not
quedó la serie es que tampoco hay no hay
much of the mystery behind Carl bad
mucho del misterio detrás de carl mala
no the mystery behind  calm down land
no el misterio detrás de calma land
you know what rip is that it's over that
sabes cuál es rip que se acabó que la
people got tired and stopped entering that's it that's
gente se cansó y dejó de entrar ya está
the big mystery or rather it doesn't
ese es el gran misterio o sea es que no
exist this is not like Maria's documentary let's
hay esto no es como el documental de
see let's watch Auro's channel
a ver vamos a ver el canal de auro
damn look what's happening to him is like what happened to me
ostias mira le está pasando como a mí
that the channel appears
que aparece el canal
well of course the channel is
bueno claro es que el canal es
secondary it's not called it's called gold it's
secundario no se llama se llama oro se
called Aurum play all together let's
llama aurum play todo junto
see
a ver
host I [ __ ] on the host
[__] me cago en la [__]
I [ __ ] on the host [ __ ]
me cago en la [__] [__]
crazy you know what I've done
loco sabéis lo que he hecho
juanjo cadena blog can
juanjo cadena blog
you imagine having done in each video let's
te imaginas teniendo hecho en cada vídeo
see calmly the man there
a ver en calma la hombre
are fewer
son menos
yes yes the truth is that yes of
sí sí la verdad que sí
course it's not that it's not that it's not that they
claro
are denying
no es que no es que se esté desmintiendo
what the others are saying but it is
lo que están diciendo los otros pero sí
noticeable how people have been
que se nota como la gente pues ha ido
losing interest in that series
dejando el interés por esa serie
which by the way
que por cierto
now that I'm watching this here
ahora que estoy viendo esto aquí
in this video minutes but if you want we
en este vídeo minutos pero si queréis
start others in this one there was also a
empezamos otras en este también había un
cameo it's in this one in which I have a
cameo es en éste en el que tengo un
change in the videos of this one between the
cambio en los vídeos de ésta entre la
left to duck in this video I
izquierda para agacharte en este vídeo
don't remember in what minutes okay Auron
no me acuerdo en qué minutos vale auron
said  savioli beira this is how
decía savioli beira así se tiene que ver
the classroom should look, not like yours, you can see that
el aula no como a ti que se te ve que
Darcos Oslo, its name is an invention, what I do
darcos oslo su nombre invento es lo que
n't know is if I don't know in what minutes it doesn't
no sé si no sé en qué minutos no lo
look for it now let's finish this that is
busca ahora vamos a terminar esto que se
getting out of hand okay click
nos está yendo de las manos vales clic
on Vegeta minutes 2 with 30 he looks
de vegeta minutos 2 con 30 se le ve
upset
molesto
let's see my old lady
vamos a ver mi viejecita
my old age and it is very clear in this place
mi vejez y está muy claro en este sitio
of those that I consider the most that would get
de los que más considero yo que se
wet would be vegetal and willy but
mojarían sería vegetal y willy pero
above all vegetal
sobre todo vegetal
bg is very clear that I did notice
bg está muy clarinete eso sí lo notaba
in the dream
en el sueño
and witch in fact and the
y bruja de hecho y se ha activado el
group of this one from Karbala has been activated they have criticized
grupo de este de kárbala han criticado
here he is talking to us but there is
por aquí nos está hablando pero no hay
nothing concrete we are there with certain
nada concreto estamos ahí con ciertas
doubts about several things because I had
dudas de varias cosas porque yo tenía
some things in mind in the end they were others it is
pensado unas cosas al final fueron otras
simply that we have to adjust and
simplemente hay que hay que ajustar y
that there are many of us so we have to
que somos muchos entonces tenemos que
be all comfortable if something is done as it is
estar todos a gusto si se hace algo como
done or if there will be a season or that
se hace o si habrá una temporada o que
endorses ok now okay
avala ok ahora vale
let's see and let's give it some stick
vamos a ver y vamos a darle leña al mono
and I don't know
y yo tampoco
in this clip either I don't know if maybe he won't
en este clip no sé si a lo mejor no
know how to appreciate it more but I  what I see
sabrá apreciar más pero yo lo que veo yo
what I see man from here a
lo que veo que hombre desde aquí un
hug to Joel de Barro who made me
abrazo a joel de barro que me ha hecho
the whole [ __ ] video of this deal is
todo el [__] vídeo de este trato sea
literally you don't see how you've worked
literalmente no veas cómo te has currado
Joel thank you very much a hug from
joel muchísimas gracias un abrazo desde
here
aquí
that I finish it from here tell these
que la termine desde aquí decirle a esta
people that it ends in the [ __ ] series of
gente que termine en la [__] serie de
guys that they finish watching them and two things
tíos que terminen a verles y dos cosas
one and give it a like all of you who have
una y darle like todos los que habéis
come this far if you agree
llegado hasta aquí si usted de acuerdo
okay that it ends in the [ __ ] series with an
vale que termine en la [__] serie con un
ending surely you will come up with something that
final seguro que se le ocurre algo que
is an ending that is great and that will
sea un final que sea la [__] y eso va a
have opinions of visitors on every channel
tener opiniones de visita en cada canal
okay and two that you tell who was the
vale y dos que contéis quien ha sido el
impostor who has left money to see
impostor que ha dejado dinero de ver
okay that is what matters most to me the
vale eso es lo que más me importa a mí
series year you
lo de la serie año ustedes